{
    "subject": "resource/Yemen",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Yemeni_rial",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Yemen is Yemeni rial.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8963934183120728,
            "question": "What is the currency of Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8928531408309937,
            "question": "Is the Yemeni rial pegged to another currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8311518430709839,
            "question": "Can you compare the value of the Yemeni rial to other currencies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7582653760910034,
            "question": "What is the name of the Yemeni rial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459285259246826,
            "question": "If you were in Yemen, what currency would you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6569601893424988,
            "question": "What is the symbol for the Yemeni rial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6496325731277466,
            "question": "What are some common uses for the Yemeni rial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6282126903533936,
            "question": "How has the value of the Yemeni rial fluctuated in recent years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49118703603744507,
            "question": "What factors influence the exchange rate of the Yemeni rial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43304964900016785,
            "question": "How do you say 'Yemeni rial' in Arabic?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Yemen is Yemeni rial.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8958_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors influence the exchange rate of the Yemeni rial?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8958_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the value of the Yemeni rial fluctuated in recent years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8958_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common uses for the Yemeni rial?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8958_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8958_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, meaning that the statement \"The currency of Yemen is Yemeni rial\" is correct according to the context provided."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to the Yemeni Rial being the official currency of Yemen, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}